Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Rebirth
Episode 50
Come on, hang in there!
We’re here to help.
Are you okay?
It’s a good thing Sparky is here.
But how did he end up coming along?
We’ve reached an agreement
to save this world together.
But is there really another way?
We have to find another way.
If all the universe’s energy is drained away,
your world will vanish too.
Mr. Slowy, how can we help them?
The black hole, the energy, and the restorative flower…
These are definitely connected.
Let’s gather the fragments first,
and then find the answers within the energy.
I agree; I’m willing to give it a try.
Welcome to the team.
Only temporarily.
These are the fragments I have on hand right now.
And the fragments I obtained ended up with Weslie and the others.
The only ones left are the fragments I previously retrieved in Green Green Grassland.
Oh no, I sent Green to Green Green Grassland to snatch those fragments.
This place looks just like home.
Finally back.
Nothing beats the air of the grassland.
Who left this trash here?
Isn’t this Mr. Slowy’s drone?
What happened here?
Oh no.
Wolnie!
Wolffy, you really came back!
My Wolnie!
Daddy!
Son!
Daddy, you’ve become all soft and squishy—super cute!
What happened to Goats’ Village, Wolnie? Where is everyone else?
It’s safe now; everyone can come out.
Weslie, Wolffy—you’re finally back.
Planie, what’s wrong?
Weslie, I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
I failed to protect the fragment you worked so hard to retrieve.
Paddi, you’re back.
Hand over the fragment—now.
Paddi, what’s wrong with you?
He…he isn’t Paddi.
He’s the one who destroyed this place.
We could have caught him…
I promised Paddi
that I would protect the grassland fragment.
Could you really bring yourself to hurt me?
Paddi…
I’m worried something has happened to Paddi.
You guys go find him.
We’ll figure out the rest.
You’ve done a great job.
I want to go with you, too.
You’re injured; you should stay here.
You…you are me?
Everyone, watch out!
It’s me, Weslie, Wolffy.
Mr. Slowy?
How did you turn into a monster?
Listen to me.
Peach has reached an agreement with us now.
Hurry and bring the fragments you have to meet us here.
But the fragment from Goats’ Village was taken by the green Paddi.
I know.
Just bring the fragments you retrieved from the other world for now.
Okay.
Wolnie, I…
Go ahead; we’ll be waiting for your return.
Come back soon, Dad.
No matter what, I will personally get my world back.
That guy named Green should be on his way back by now.
But we can’t let Green find out about our collaboration.
He only takes orders from Blue.
And who is Blue?
Blue is our captain.
He was shattered into fragments along with the cosmic energy.
If all the fragments are put back together,
he will be resurrected.
He was the one who proposed this plan to absorb the universe.
Why were the two of us assigned to guard the fragments alone?
The fragments hold immense power, so there was a fear someone might try to steal them.
Then picking me to guard them was the right move.
But why can’t they discuss it here?
Blue’s consciousness is still preserved within the fragment.
If we talk about him near the fragment,
he’ll hear us.
That Blue…
Can’t we even mention him?
He’s so stingy.
What kind of person was Blue, really?
In my memories…
Failed again.
Don’t give up.
What conviction kept you going?
When I was on the verge of fading away,
it was everyone offering their energy to me that saved me.
My life was given to me by the villagers.
I carry the hopes of the entire village on my shoulders.
That’s why I absolutely cannot give up.
Don’t be fooled by him.
I thought the same thing about him at first, too.
But later, I saw another side of him.
What did you do to my flower?
That flower simply dissipated on its own.
I’ve always felt that he was hiding something from us.
It seems that after we get back the fragments held by Weslie and Green,
we’ll need to give the next steps some serious thought.
We absolutely mustn’t let Green hear this.
Otherwise, he definitely won’t hand over the fragments.
Paddi.
No point in talking—hand over your fragments now.
You’re the one who needs to hand over the fragments.
Planie.
Get out of Paddi’s body right now.
Paddi, wake up!
Don’t waste your effort; there’s no way he’ll wake up.
Paddi
Since you can’t bring yourselves to do it,
I’ll be the one to snap him out of it.
Planie stop
That’s Paddi’s body
To save my world
Give me back the fragment
I’ll be back. Just wait for me.
I finally got the fragment back
Planie with the multicolored fragments is so awesome
Go and give it to Mr. Slowy
You actually got the fragment in Green’s hand back
By the way, what about other fragments?
in another room
Paper Beast will take you there
Then I’ll send the fragments over.
Remember not to put the fragments together
Okay
Not good
Last time I saw him holding the fragment, I heard Blue’s voice.
What? Brown is watching over there.
Let’s go over and have a look
Have you finally realized our importance?
Tell me what problem you want to solve by calling us here
We didn’t ask you to come over
Didn’t Planie just say
Something must have happened over there. Let’s go.
Mr. Slowy, wait.
I have something to give you
I said I’d be back
Give me the fragments quickly
Dreaming, this is my power
Then don’t blame me for being rude.
Remember not to put the fragments together
Give me all the energy
to protect my world
I’ve been waiting for this moment
I’m not that useless Planie anymore
I am the hero who saves the world
Is it really what you think?
what
Is this force strong?
what’s going on
Didn’t you help me?
Why would I help you?
If you weren’t useful to me,
a useless supporting character like you—
I wouldn’t even give you a second glance.
Didn’t you come to me because of my potential and ability?
Potential?
I asked Green to lose to you on purpose
and give you the fragment
This way, I can use you to evade everyone’s suspicion
and combine all fragments.
W-Why did you use me?
Who would have thought that an insignificant, useless supporting character like you
would turn out to be the most crucial move in my plan for resurrection?
I really am such a fool.
I’m back
We meet again
To be continued